Needed their signatures.
I'm telling you, it's not a problem.
We have to wait a little.
The market's gonna turn around
and everything will be fine.
Okay. We have to sell the penthouse.
No. We don't.
-That's, that's--
-What? An actual solution?
Maybe growing up in this place,
you got used to the idea
that a solution will
just fall out of the sky. But it won't.
You've got a daughter to think of.
I've got it under control, Eleanor.
Do you want to?
Who are we kidding? You go.
Kate?
Coming in.
You shouldn't eavesdrop.
Then how would I know
what you're saying when I'm not there?
I don't know how to argue with that.
How much did you hear?
I don't want to move.
That much, huh?
-We don't have to.
-How do you know?
Mommy said things
don't just fall from the sky.
Well, yeah,
but there's always gonna be weather.
Some people forget
the one thing they can control,
the choices they make in the face of it.
What would you do in a hurricane?
I would do what I always do.
Protect you.
Now, why don't you go have
some lunch with your mom?
Think fast.
I'll be downstairs in my office.
Mommies can be
pretty fun, too, you know.
I bet you didn't know I could do this.
Made you smile.
Come on.
Why don't you go grab the Checkers?
We can liven things up.
-All right. Yeah.
-Yeah?
Okay, I'm going downstairs,
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Mommy!
Mommy? Mommy, what's happening?
Daddy, where are you?
Dad?
Dad. Daddy, where are you?
Mommy!
Kate!
We have to get out of here.
Is Daddy okay?
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Daddy!
I'm so sorry, my dear.
What if they come back?
They won't come back.
How do you know?
Because the heroes
showed them what would happen.
And even though this is scary,
I'm still the luckiest woman in the world
because I have
the greatest little girl in the world.
Who is not that little.
I need to protect us.
Kate, that's my job.
Okay?
Whatever you need, I'm here for you.
I need a bow and arrow.
Ugh! Come on!
Kate, be careful.
If we get caught, you're definitely
gonna be kicked off the archery team.
Yeah, I know. But a bet's a bet, Greer.
Okay, so the real question.
Does the bell swing back and forth,
or the dangly thingy swing back and forth?
It's obviously the bell.
See? I would disagree.
I think it's the dangly thingy.
Nice outfit by the way, Kate.
Yeah, well,
sometimes, you gotta dress the part.
I know it's a bet,
but are you sure
that arrow won't damage it?
No.
Well, that was a bit of a letdown.
Okay, you know what, just hang on.
Hang on.
Let me just fix this. Give me a second.
Oh, my God!
That was amazing! Wow!
Nice, Kate.
That's fine.
Right? I mean, it gives it character.
All famous bells have cracks in them.
All right, that's, uh, that's not great.
But it could be worse.
This is bad.
Hold it!
Dad?
Did you turn your hearing aid off?
No, honey, I know what happens.
I was there.
You know who wasn't there?
Is that guy.
Ant-Man.
You look pretty cool though.
That's a plus.
I'll be right back.
-Hmm.
Oh, uh, a selfie
would be really rad, dude.
My kids would flip.
I mean, you're their absolute favorite.
Yeah, uh...
Now's not really the appropriate time.
Is now a better time?
Wow.
-Hey, are you okay?
-Oh, hey, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. I, uh, just wanted
to come out for some, uh...
Some fresh air, is all.
You know it's fine if you don't
wanna watch the show. I mean...
I know everyone misses her, but...
she was your best friend. It's...
Come here, baby.
This whole thing
is a bit ridiculous, isn't it?
A lot ridiculous.
-The Hulk part was great.
-Yeah, I liked the Hulk.
Hey, Dad. Hey, Lila.
Hey, guys! What's up?
What are you doing here?
Why is everyone singing
and dancing about everything?
I don't know.
But it's Christmas in New York.
And we're out of here. Right?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
-NATHANIEL: All right.
-Let's show Mom what she's missing.
-NATHANIEL: Yeah.
-Come on, bud.
Hey, Mom!
Hey, honey! I missed you.
-Uh, are you in the city?
-KATE: Yeah, I, uh, I am.
I was gonna stop by my place
and then come see you.
Will you come here first, please?
Jack's over.
I want to talk to you about something.
Okay, uh, okay.
I'll, uh, see you soon, Mom.
Good evening, Miss Bishop.
How's it going? Good?
Wife, kids, all good?
Wonderful, wonderful, Merry Christmas!
-ELEANOR: Hi, sweetie.
-KATE: Hi, Mom.
There you are.
Oh, you look amazing.
What are we looking all fancy for?
Charity auction.
-Ugh.
-I know, right?
All those poor people and nonprofits
relying on the more fortunate.
That is not what I meant.
As much as I love having
you home for the holidays,
I'm not thrilled that I'm about
to replace an irreplaceable clock tower.
It was a bell tower.
The Dean said it had a bell and a clock,
and overachiever that you are,
you managed to destroy both.
What can I do to make it better, Mom?
I started by cancelling your credit cards,
and we're going to have a much longer talk
about this tower that you destroyed,
without joking.
I know young people
think they're invincible,
and rich people think they're invincible
and you've always been both.
So take it from someone
who hasn't, you're not.
You will get hurt.
So please, don't go out looking for it.
Sorry, Mom.
Sorry.
Okay.
You get that from your father, you know.
Why don't you start making it up to me
by putting on that red dress in
your bedroom and coming with me tonight?
All right, well, um,
on another note,
I got a new one for the case.
U.S. Open Martial Art Championship.
You're amazing. I still remember
when you got your black belt at 15.
We might have to retire some from
when you were little to make room. Huh?
-I like those.
-ELEANOR: I do, too, hon.
I do, too.
What's with all the swords, Mom?
Hon, uh, there have been a few changes
while you were away this semester.
Ta-da!
Jack?
Oh.
What an unexpected surprise.
All surprises are unexpected.
That can't be right. Is it?
Nice to see you again, Katie.
That was in your mouth.
So it was.
We cannot be late, so go change.
Meet us at the hotel
and we'll talk there. Okay?
-Shall we?
-Let's.
We'll see you at the party.
See you there, honey.
Lots more to talk about.
You look like a maniac.
You're a total crazy person.
Is anybody else hungry?
For some more, like, some more crabs
or maybe get four more crabs?
-What do you think?
-Yes. I could eat three.
-No.
-COOPER: Come on, Dad,
you ordered food for 30 people.
You're going to puke if you have any more.
And if he pukes,
you two are cleaning it up.
I'm not cleaning it up.
Hey, you know what?
You know what's right down the street?
The Christmas tree.
The biggest one you'll see in your life.
It's enormous!
You want to see that after this?
-Yeah!
-Yeah! Let's go.
-Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Momma callin'. Momma's calling. Say "Hi!"
-Hi, Mom!
-Hi, Momma!
Hey, guys! How are ya?
I miss you so much!
-We miss you, too.
-LAURA: How was the show?
It was, uh-- It's over. It was big.
-We left halfway through.
-There you go.
Oh, no!
You guys all good?
Uh, yeah,
it'd be easier if you were here.
I'd be less likely to strangle these kids.
The whole point was for you
to spend time with the kids.
No, I'm kidding.
We're having a really good time.
-We miss you.
-I miss you.
-I can't wait to see you guys tomorrow.
-LILA: Bye, Mom!
-LILA: Bye, Mom! Love you!
-Bye, Mom.
-Talk to you later. See you soon.
-NATHANIEL: Bye-bye.
Well, look, it's six days
until Christmas, okay?
We're gonna do a lot of activities.
What's your favorite one?
-Um, gingerbread house.
-We're doing that!
What do you got?
Uh, Christmas movie marathon.
Movie marathon, awesome!
-Uh, ugly sweaters.
-Ugly Christmas sweaters!
We have to decorate the tree.
There's a thousand things to do.
It's going to be amazing,
but most important thing,
we're going to do it all together.
No. Not holding their hands.
Hold your brothers' hands.
I love you guys.
Love you, too.
It's going to be
the best Barton Christmas ever!
All right?
-Please.
-Yeah.
Dinner is on us.
-Thank you.
-Oh, that's, that's not necessary.
It's necessary. You saved our city.
Oh. Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
-NATHANIEL: Thank you!
-COOPER: Thank you.
Uh, get back to work.
-Excuse me dear, would you--
-Sorry, I'm not a waitress.
You're the little Bishop girl.
Yes, I am.
-Armand. Armand Duquesne.
-Ah.
You used to come to my brownstone
for brunch.
Oh, build your own blintz bar.
Precisely.
You know, it's unfair.
I never looked
that good in a tuxedo in my life.
I'd appreciate it if you wear something
a little more lady-like for the wedding,
so we won't be competing.
What wedding?
You don't know?
Eleanor and Jack.
Oh! Those secretive little love birds!
-WAITER: Can I offer you some champagne?
-Thank you!
Believe me, I've done everything
in my power to talk him out of it.
When he gets something
set in that little mind of his,
he can be quite determined.
Oh.
Seems like he won the jackpot.
You think so?
So does he.
I'm not so sure.
Armand, I wanna go home. I'm bored.
That's no way to talk, Armand.
That's not the way you were brought up.
Come and say hello to Miss Bishop.
Hey.
Hello.
Another Armand, I see.
Yes. I'm Armand the third
and he's Armand the seventh.
I believe that's quite sufficient.
Well, uh, I'm gonna
make my excuses because it seems that
you need to have a chat
with your prize of a mother.
Come on, Armand. Come on, boy!
You're engaged?
Oh, well, I guess
the beans are out of the bag.
Well, can we have a little moment?
Oh, of course, it's almost time
for my other engagement anyway.
Bye.
Babe, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry you found out this way.
I don't know, Mom, this is just like...
-Fast.
-Yeah, yeah, it's fast, yes.
But, you know, it's kind of nice
being swept up in the romance of it.
Is there a part of you
that could be happy for me?
Yes.
Yes, Mom, of course.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry,
I wanted to tell you first. I'm sorry.
-I'm going to get some air, Mom.
-I understand.
Yep.
-Come back and find me, okay?
-KATE: Yeah.
-Hi.
Heck of a party, huh?
I should've known
that this empire of yours
would be built on a lie.
By myself from the ground up.
So whatever you think you saw is not true.
Don't insult my intelligence.
You're frankly insulting us both.
-I know what I saw.
-You are all just--
Don't you try that on me.
I gave you an opportunity
to explain yourself.
I don't want to argue with you.
I've got powerful friends, too.
The kind you don't want to mess with.
Please.
Armand!
See you at Christmas dinner.
Mom, what was that about?
Is that guy threatening you?
I honestly-- I have no idea.
Why are you lurking in the hallways?
-KATE: I was outside getting air.
-Come back to the party.
-KATE: Okay. All right.
-Okay.
-KATE: Be right there.
-ELEANOR: All right.
-Be right back.
-Okay.
Gary wants you to bring
these down, right away.
-Just these two?
-These two.
This seat is taken.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please be seated, and we will begin.
I've reached
my breaking point with your fiancée.
Things are about to get very ugly.
Why don't we leave Eleanor alone,
you old goat.
For our first item
of the evening,
we will be traveling back in time.
We'll start the bidding for this
magnificent skull at $2 million.
Do I hear $2 million?
Bidder bidder, two-point-one.
I got $2 million,
do I hear two-point-one?
Two-point-one, thank you so much, sir.
Do I hear two-point-two?
-Do I hear two-point-two?
-Excuse me?
Hey, excuse me!
Oh, perfect!
-Oh.
-Great.
I was supposed
to be the only one working here.
Gary? Gary sent me to work here.
So maybe if you want to bother Gary...
You're doing great. Okay.
Two million seven,
now two million eight.
I've got two million seven
right here, going once.
I've got two-point-seven going twice.
Sold for $2.7 million.
Thank you. And I will remind you
that this is for home display only.
And you have no idea where you got it.
Who told you to come down here?
Gary.
I'm Gary.
What's your name?
You see that's the problem, Gary,
you don't even know my name.
You know, uh, this is,
this is not gonna work out. I quit.
You can't quit. Hold on.
Where did she go?
Excuse me.
Come on, let's go. Move.
Don't forget your positions.
Mine's on the left.
Yeah, bro.
Get ready.
Up next,
we have a very special piece.
An artifact recovered from
the wreckage of the Avengers compound.
Now you may recall the Ronin decimated
the criminal underworld of the city,
almost completely annihilating the status
and power of the head of organized crime.
The Ronin brought
a brutal form of justice to his victims,
and his identity continues
to remain a mystery to this very day.
Now you can own
this one-of-a-kind retractable sword,
and we'll start the bidding at $200,000.
Do I hear $200,000? $200,000,
bidder bidder, do I hear $250,000?
$250,000, thank you, sir.
Do I hear $300,000?
$300,000, looking for $350,000.
What are you doing, you dope?
I'm buying that sword.
You don't have 300 grand.
No, but I'll inherit it one day, won't I?
-$350,000.
-$350,000, right here in the front.
Do we go to $400,000?
Let's go to four. Four, thank you so much.
At $400,000, do I hear $450,000?
Moving to two.
Okay, everybody ready?
$440,000, do I hear $450,000?
$450,000 up front. Looking for $475,000.
Come on, ladies and gentlemen.
This sword belonged to the infamous Ronin.
$475,000.
$475,000, bidder bidder,
do I hear $500,000?
I've got $475,000 here, it's going once.
$475,000 is going twice.
Sold for $475,000.
Up next, we have lot number 3-0-9.
The companion piece, the Ronin suit.
Help! Please help!
Security!
We're stuck in here!
We've got 90 seconds
to find the watch.
Everything else is secondary.
Let's go, bro.
-MAN 3: Spread out. Let's go, let's go.
Find the watch!
Where is it? Where is it?
Come on! We're running out of time!
Come on. Let's go.
Grab my hand!
I can't see.
Do you know who I am?
Hello.
Quick, hurry!
Everyone get out of here!
I see him! I see him, there!
Okay.
Come on, Kate.
He disappeared!
I'm telling you, it was the Ronin!
He's here somewhere, bro!
Keep looking!
Oh, shit!
He's getting away!
Darling!
-Where's Kate? She won't answer the phone.
-I don't know.
-Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
-Ronin?
The watch. I found it.
Hey!
Get off me!
I'm gonna get you, you dumb dog!
-Ow! Aah!
I kill you!
Hey!
-KATE: Wait!
Wait! Wait, wait, wait! Wait!
-Oh, wait! Wait! No, no, no.
Kazi! Kazi!
-We gotta go!
-MAN 2: Let's go, bro!
Kazi! We go now! Come on!
Let's get to the van
and go after her.
You were right about the tree, Dad.
It was amazing.
I want one that big.
It wouldn't fit
in our house, dummy.
Please, please, please?
It's a little late for TV, guys.
I've gotta pack.
Ay, ay, ay.
We are following a breaking news story.
A high society gala rocked by an explosion
when it went off at Park Avenue
and 68th Street tonight.
The cause of the explosion
is still under investigation.
But witnesses captured cell phone footage
of a masked assailant fleeing the scene.
Check it out.
A ninja saved a dog.
Authorities believe
the assailant could be the Ronin...
Isn't that awesome, Dad?
...who terrorized
organized crime in New York and elsewhere.
This is the first
potential sighting of the Ronin in years.
Welcome to my apartment.
Whoa. Okay, that was, that was crazy.
But we're safe. We're safe.
Okay, what is going on with Armand?
Threatening my mom
and buying black market swords?
Do you think he's connected
to the break-in somehow?
-Food. You want food. Uh, of course. Oh.
Uh...
Okay, listen. Just hang on.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna get you some food.
Uh...
Pizza? You want some pizza?
Okay.
Have some. Go on.
Good boy. Wow.
You like pizza.
I've got to figure out
what's up with Armand.
Okay.
Do not destroy this apartment.
Monogrammed butterscotch?
Armand?
Oh, God!
Mr. Duquesne?
I have your dry cleaning,
and I brought dinner.
Where do you think you're going?
We only want to talk.
Hey,
we got little surprise for you.
We've got eyes everywhere.
We missed you, Ronin.
We got you now, bro.
Why you makin' it so tough on us, bro?
Sorry.
Oh, come on.
Come on!
You're... You're Hawkeye!
And who the hell are you?